Why?
Afraid to search?
Then let him do it for you.
It's time for you to taste it.
This...
This is...
Guard the door.
Understood.
[Eclipse in the Lost City; Episode 5]
Who ordered you to do this?
Speak!
No.
I didn't do it.
Do you think I'd believe that?
You established yourself in Ningcheng
with those goods, didn't you?
Regarding my father's death,
whoever benefits the most
is the killer.
I only took the goods.
But I didn't kill
Qinglong.
Stop making excuses.
The old chief trusted you so much.
Back then,
he saved your life with a silver needle.
But you bite the hand that feeds you.
You've been by the old chief's side
for so many years.
I'm afraid you’ve had ulterior motives
all along.
How dare you
talk nonsense!
I didn't kill the old chief.
It's come to this,
and you still won't confess?
Lu Ye.
You will regret this.
Do you really think you can trap me?
I've already prepared a backup plan.
A backup plan?
All your men are here.
Which one are you talking about?
Young Master.
I really shouldn't have
embezzled those goods.
Please forgive me.
Give me one more chance.
Alright.
Then let's follow the rules of
the Qingtian Gang.
Three stabs.
If you survive them,
I'll spare your life.
No.
The first stab is for your disloyalty.
Young Master, I know I was wrong.
The second stab is for your cruelty.
I won't do it again.
The third stab
is for your injustice.
Let the blood flow.
Once the filth in your bones is drained,
consider it your atonement.
As long as you can step out of this door,
you and the Qingtian Gang are even.
Just one step away.
What a pity.
Seems like you're out of luck.
Young Master,
spare my life.
The old chief wouldn't want to see you
become like this.
You're right.
He really didn't want me
to get blood on my hands.
Too bad.
People change.
Aunt Que.
I'm sorry.
I had to confirm who was involved.
It was a misunderstanding.
Sorry for startling you.
Young Master.
This...
Please accept it.
I...
You've worked hard all these years.
Consider it a thank you
on behalf of my father.
Young Master,
my condolences.
You did a good job today.
You flatter me, Young Master.
They don't know you've lost your memory.
Originally,
I just wanted to use your title as sheriff
to bluff them.
I was even afraid you'd get stage fright.
I didn't expect you to perform so well.
It's all thanks to your teaching,
Young Master.
Wrong.
It wasn't me.
You deserve the credit.
Tell me, is your acting just that good,
or
have you recovered your memory?
No.
I still can't remember anything.
Is that so?
Then why do you remember this?
Oh no.
Guard the door.
Give me an explanation.
Young Master,
I...
I didn't even notice your action
at the time.
I just guessed
that Qinglong would run away,
so I stopped him first.
Young Master,
did I do something wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault for acting on my own.
Forget it.
I was overthinking.
Let's drink.
Young Master,
please.
To the Qingtian Gang.
Who is it?
It's you again, Shen Tianbai.
Are you crazy?
You skipped class.
Go back to class.
What’s it to you
whether I go to class or not?
Who are you to tell me what to do?
You think I want to babysit you?
But the school said
your dad funds my scholarship.
He only asked me to do one thing.
And that's to keep an eye on you.
Can't you just make something up?
The old man believes whatever you say
anyway.
Why should I lie for you?
Go call for help.
Without me,
how will you claim credit from my father?
Trying to call for help?
It's the same trick every time.
I've seen it twice.
Even a fool could guess it.
You...
Let's go.
You can still make it
to the afternoon class.
Let me go.
Since when do you get to tell me
what to do?
Let me go.
Are you awake?
How could Mr. Lu have a son like you?
What else can you do
besides spending money?
Then why don't you just go be his son?
He only likes sons like you anyway.
What's wrong?
We're even.
Childish.
Yes, yes.
You are the most mature.
Prude.
Your father is right.
You are just a useless piece of trash.
Right.
He looks down on me anyway.
Sometimes I really envy you.
No parents, no one to control you.
You deserve it.
Likewise.
Alright.
Now we don't have to go to class.
In your dreams.
There's another class in the afternoon.
We can make it.
You want to go to class like this?
I can say
we went to do a good deed.
When did you learn to lie?
I learned it from you.
The mole is caught.
Tonight,
we can all get a good night's sleep.
Drink.
You think this can trap me?